[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[In my prime]
[Episode 26]
Do you think I'm
too full of myself
and too useless?
I can't even protect my own brand
and employees.
What kind of boss am I?
Why am I even running a company?
Shut it down then.
You should believe in yourself.
You have courage, your own ideas,
and a sharp sense
of the clothing market.
All these mean that
you can definitely become
a qualified, good boss.
Starting a business
always has its ups and downs.
But don't worry.
No matter how big the storm
our company faces,
I will surely be there with you
to the very end.
Are you moved? Don't cry.
No, I'm not.
What do you mean by being there
with me to the very end?
You're a partner.
That's what you should do.
Yeah, yeah.
We're now
in the same boat.
Therefore,
I have to give it my all
and share weal and woe with you.
But I'm tired.
I want to take a rest.
I'll leave the company to you for now.
Once you clear the inventory,
you can take all the money left.
Okay.
It's good to take a rest.
Let's go. I'll escort you home.
♪ But your shoulders allow me
to drop my disguise ♪
♪ If there's nothing left tomorrow ♪
♪ I still want to watch the sunset
with you ♪
This one.
And this one.
And then
submit.
See?
Online shopping isn't that hard, huh?
It used to be so hard
to get you to buy some clothes
with your own money.
Now that you know our daughter's
business is struggling,
you bought
several sets at once.
You've got clothes
for all 4 seasons.
I'm killing two birds with one stone,
helping both our daughter and son.
Well,
they are running
this online store together,
aren't they?
It's not easy for young people
to start a business.
We can't let them lose
every penny they've put into it
because of that stupid mess.
A mother's selfless love.
Even I am touched.
Enough.
Qi Shi said
she'd be back for dinner later.
I bought a fish for her.
Go clean it.
I'll cook it for her.
See?
It's too late.
She's already back.
Coming.
Sweetie,
welcome back.
Welcome back.
-Dad.
-You must be tired.
Go get some rest.
I'll cook fish for you later.
Are you thirsty?
Would you like me
to wash some fruit for you?
I'm hungry and thirsty right now.
I just want to be spoon-fed.
Okay, just a moment.
I will go wash them.
Being spoon-fed is no problem,
but you have to pour your own water.
You rarely come back home,
so you have to do something.
I'm going to cook fish for you.
Si.
Come here.
I have something to tell everyone.
Our company's not doing well
currently.
Judging from the financial data,
we can't make up for the losses
anytime soon
through normal marketing.
The priority now
is to deal with all this inventory
and customer returns.
I've thought about it.
We need to categorize the products.
For the ones that sell well,
we can offer appropriate discounts.
For the harder-to-sell ones,
we can bundle them at a low price
to sell through other channels.
This way, we can clear the inventory
and recover funds quickly
to ease the financial pressure
on our company.
What do you think?
This is a solution plan
I've put together.
Take a look.
Almost there.
Excuse me, may I ask
where you bought your jacket?
I just got it from an online store.
Did you buy other pieces
from that store?
Nope.
Could you tell me
why you bought it?
Did you like how it looked,
or was there some other reason?
Why so many questions?
You, too?
Why did you want
to play ring toss
with our eyesight?
It was exactly because of my bad eyesight.
When I was little
and walked past these stalls with my mom,
she never let me play.
The more she said no,
the more I wanted to play.
How would I know if I didn't try?
What if I was like a genius girl
in a comic book,
with the power
to break through innate obstacles?
But it turns out...
It turns out
that we're just ordinary people.
You're not ordinary at all.
My mom said that for albinos,
just maintaining
a normal daily life is good enough.
Don't even think about doing
anything earth-shattering.
But you actually opened a shop.
How is opening a shop
earth-shattering?
Now I feel like
I-I just don't know how to run a shop.
I only had passion,
rushed forward blindly,
and ended up
betraying everyone's trust.
But the fact that you asked me
all those questions
means
you haven't given up on this shop
and still want to do better, right?
Let me think.
When I bought this jacket,
I just searched a random keyword,
and the site recommended
a bunch of similar ones.
Then why did you choose this one?
Because...
it was cheap.
So
there's nothing special
about its design,
huh?
It's merely
an ordinary jacket,
not even as special as we are.
Look at our skin
and hair.
We just stand out in any crowd.
Order 5748153357, right?
I see it.
I see you put the reason
for return
as a defective product, right?
A big sale for women's fashion!
Come on! Take a look!
Come on, beautiful. Come and take a look.
Women's fashion.
[Prime Era]
Have you forgotten when you were little?
You kept your wrist still
and ended up getting beaten up.
You've been staying at home
for a week now, right?
What's going on with your company?
No idea. Cao Xin is managing it.
You can't
just leave it all to him
and rest at home every day.
What?
Are you caring about your biological son?
My biological son doesn't
eat and live on my dime every day,
without doing anything.
Do I owe you this from a past life?
Huh?
Mom, don't deny it.
I was just wondering back then.
You were really biased towards Cao Xin.
He ate
all the buns
we only made once
every half a month.
Girl, you're so petty.
That was ages ago,
and you still remember?
Then how about
all those meals I cooked for you?
How many sweaters did I knit for you?
How much did I worry about you?
Don't knit little flowers for me anymore.
I'm a grown-up now.
And knitting little flowers
is quite a hassle.
How pretty this little flower is.
It's just so pretty.
I think...
it was when you were in primary school.
You started to care about your looks.
You thought the sweaters I knitted for you
were ugly.
Then I...
I tried to figure out a way.
I figured it out
by knitting a little flower like this
on the cuff
or the chest for you,
so you could look a bit prettier
and a bit special
when you wear it.
♪ When the world falls still ♪
Actually...
♪ There is nothing left to argue ♪
In my eyes,
♪ I stand at the crossroads ♪
whether you're white-haired
♪ While memories flood the station ♪
or blue-eyed,
you are one of a kind.
My daughter is the best.
♪ Who doesn't want to be born ♪
♪ In a world of love? ♪
♪ But how do you keep enduring ♪
Mom.
♪ When every hope has come apart ♪
Thank you.
Thank me for what?
Time for lunch.
Come on, lend me the sweater.
Lend it to me.
W-What for?
I'm not eating, Dad.
I'll come back and eat another day.
I haven't finished knitting yet!
You're not eating?
I figured out a way.
The core of originality is innovation,
♪ Moonlight casts a glow
on the windowsill ♪
♪ While shadows linger close by ♪
a one-of-a-kind
brand concept.
I kept talking about
♪ I've slowly learned to confess ♪
originality before,
but all I did was
♪ My loneliness to myself ♪
produce the clothes designed
by Yuanyuan.
But I never thought about
♪ Who'd like to grow up ♪
which designs
aligned with my brand,
♪ Making the best of the hard times? ♪
or
what unique features of my brand
♪ But some people are just born unlucky ♪
could be integrated into the designs.
♪ And never favored by fate ♪
Look.
This flower
♪ The gale and the heavy rain ♪
was knitted onto the sweater
♪ The faded traces at the alley entrance ♪
by my mom.
I was born with albinism.
♪ Why does this world ♪
♪ Have to slander ♪
I did feel self-abased.
♪ What I believe again? ♪
But my mom never saw me that way.
♪ Still, I will love; still, I may lose ♪
She thinks
I'm her one-of-a-kind daughter.
Therefore,
♪ Still, I will not give up ♪
every sweater of mine is
adorned with a little flower like this.
♪ Even if I look foolish
in the spotlight ♪
This is the value
♪ I will choose to be the only exception ♪
that a brand and its concept
can bring to its products.
♪ No matter how slight the chance ♪
I got it.
We need to find
the true brand concept
♪ I will reach for it ♪
of Prime Era.
♪ Because my life ♪
Only then can we make
♪ Deserves a brighter future ♪
a one-of-a-kind, original brand
that fears no copycats.
Exactly.
♪ I've stumbled through the years ♪
♪ Giving it my all, and then waiting ♪
♪ Who in the world doesn't have ♪
♪ Some unspeakable sorrow? ♪
♪ Through the shadows, through the heat ♪
♪ What is there to fight? ♪
♪ Why does this world ♪
♪ Finally turn the attention ♪
♪ To me this time? ♪
♪ Still, I will love; still, I may lose ♪
♪ Still, I will not give up ♪
♪ Even if I look foolish
in the spotlight ♪
♪ I will choose to be the only exception ♪
♪ No matter how slight the chance ♪
♪ Even if it's never been
written in the stars ♪
♪ I will still ♪
♪ Struggle and try again ♪
♪ For even in the darkest night ♪
♪ There is ♪
♪ A light kindled for me ♪
Do you think
this will fit me?
It will.
Miss Qi,
congratulations on the great success
of your press conference.
I noticed
your unique look today.
I wonder if it's related
to the latest collection
of your brand.
Not long ago, Xinran
accused you of plagiarism,
which caused quite a stir.
Your brand almost shut down
because of it.
How can you make sure
that similar issues
won't arise again
with the new product launch?
Thank you all for your questions.
As you can see,
I have albinism.
Indeed,
others see it as a disease,
a defect.
I also know it.
However,
in my mother's eyes,
I am her one-of-a-kind treasure.
Thanks to her love,
I've gradually
realized that my differences
are exactly what makes me unique.
You've all seen
this season's new collection.
The inspiration
for the cuff button design
comes from the world
as I see it.
It's something ordinary people
can never experience.
I want
to integrate this unique experience
into my designs,
making every piece of clothing
unique and irreplaceable.
So to those plagiarists,
I want to say,
you can copy the styles,
but you can't copy my soul.
So today,
I also want to say this to everyone,
including those
who once slandered me—
time
will tell.
Prime Era has risen from the ashes.
That's my sister.
Well said.
I'd like to state once again that
Prime Era is
a women's fashion brand
dedicated to originality.
Resilience, independence,
and being undefined
are its brand DNA.
Next, I will make public
every single design sketch
that has been copyrighted.
I will post them
on our brand's official Weibo account.
Anyone in the industry is welcome
to come for exchange and learning.
Meanwhile,
Prime Era
has also joined
the Garment Industry Association.
As a member of the industry,
I am willing to do my part
to protect originality.
Thank you.
-Alright.
-Thank you, Miss Qi.
Miss Qi,
may I
ask you
a few personal questions?
Miss Qi,
it won't take much of your time.
Is 10 minutes okay?
Just 10 minutes.
Sorry, guys,
we can only answer
brand-related questions.
Why do you go everywhere with an umbrella?
I'm just worried you'll get sunburned.
Look, your skin's red again after just
a little time in the sun.
You don't take care of yourself.
I know.
Why are you more nagging than my mom?
I need to tell you something.
Go back to Qingwu with me this weekend.
Why go back all of a sudden?
I bought back
our old family house.
Where did you get the money?
Didn't you leave
the company to me, ask me
to clear the inventory,
and promise me all the money left?
Isn't that still my money?
My money! My money! My money!
Our money. It's ours.
Ours!
Thank you, thank you.
Okay.
Doudou,
you've gained weight again.
Cao,
come set the bowls.
Okay, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Have a seat inside.
Come on, sit over here.
Sit over here.
Thank you.
Okay, okay.
-Cao Xin.
-Dongfang!
Dongfang!
Congratulations.
Here, take the red envelope.
Thank you.
What a grand occasion.
Yes. Come in, please.
Come on in.
Have a seat.
Look at the time.
The banquet is about to start.
Why aren't they here yet?
Call and ask them.
I'll call Qi Shi.
Okay.
Dad,
there they come!
You're the last ones we were waiting for.
Aihua.
Qinglian.
Congratulations.
Glad you could make it.
Come on in, please.
Come in.
Oh, right.
No need. No need.
Take it.
Take it. Just take it.
Well...
This is quite a big one.
Come on, come on in.
Come on in.
Aihua!
Let me do it.
Lingzhi.
Cao Xin, come here.
Qi Shi, sit next to your dad.
Let's sit next to each other.
And Qi Shi,
I haven't seen you in ages!
Come on... Alright...
Just a little bit.
This is enough.
Director Zhang.
Hello.
Long time no see.
Did you miss me?
Pour the wine.
Okay.
Come on.
How rare it is to see you.
I'm really happy today.
We've returned to our hometown.
It's an auspicious day.
Thank you all for coming.
You grace our home.
Come on,
let's start the banquet!
Make yourselves at home.
-Come on.
-Cheers!
-Cheers.
Come on. Cheers.
Dongfang.
Congratulations.
You didn't raise your son for nothing.
Look,
he bought this old house
back for you just a few years
after graduation.
Congrats.
Let me raise a glass to you.
Thank you, Director.
Cao Xin is just outstanding.
Cheers.
Aihua.
No moving, no moving.
Just sit there.
I'll go over there.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
Look.
I have heard that your bun shop
in our provincial capital is doing great.
You must have made good money.
When will you come back
and settle down in Qingwu?
Why come back to Qingwu?
The provincial capital
is like a gold mine.
It's perfect in every way.
Why would they come back?
Exactly.
No, he's just talking nonsense.
The provincial capital isn't good at all.
Once the doors are closed,
no one talks to anyone.
I don't even have anyone to talk to.
I'm suffocating.
Really?
That's true.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Glad you're finally back.
We're old
and just can't leave.
Let me have another piece of fish.
Well,
Qi Zhi.
I heard your current company
is doing really well, right?
E-commerce is booming lately, right?
So my freight company
is benefiting from it.
I'm planning to open
another freight company
here in Qingwu.
Really?
Qi Zhi has really made it.
His business keeps expanding.
The Qi family's ancestors must be
blessing him!
Come on, don't say that.
I work from dawn to dusk every day,
and you're giving all the credit
to my ancestors?
My son is capable
and has brought honor to the Qi family.
If any of you are
looking for a job in the future,
just go to him.
The pay is definitely
better than at the mine.
Really?
Stop bragging.
You make it sound like
we own a mine.
Let me propose a toast to everyone.
-Come on, cheers.
-Cheers.
Cheers.
Congratulations.
I was just trying to support my son.
Honey.
How about we move back, too?
Look at all the neighbors.
It's so lively when we're together.
Cao Xin,
are you seeing anyone?
How about
I set you up with someone?
Yeah.
No need.
My uncle is already into someone.
For real?
What did you just say?
Here, have a chicken drumstick
and stop talking.
Here, have one more, one more.
That's not right.
You should bring
the one you like back for us to meet.
Mom, mom, mom.
Stop being so gossipy.
I-I'm just concerned...
Instead of worrying about others,
worry about me, your own son,
and find me a girlfriend.
Cheers.
Director Zhang.
For all these years,
there's been
something weighing on my mind.
Go ahead.
Tell me...
Director Zhang, tell me,
how was my performance at the mine
back then?
It was good.
Good, right?
Yep.
I had been an advanced worker
for so many years,
right?
Indeed.
You were the leader
in charge of HR.
I...
I just don't get it.
How could you just listen to
a few words from Cao Dongfang
and lay off a...
a veteran miner
like me,
an excellent veteran miner
who once won medals?
Aihua,
let me tell you...
I just don't get it.
You've got a huge misunderstanding.
Back then,
the layoff list was decided
by the director.
Besides, you were laid off
not because Cao Dongfang played dirty
behind your back.
He even went to the director's office
to speak up for you.
Aihua,
I'm sorry.
I was the one who submitted
that list back then.
If I had spoken up for you a bit,
maybe...
How about this?
I'll down 3 shots
to apologize to you,
okay?
-Come on.
Nice wine.
Eat up.
Take your time.
Dongfang.
Go ahead...
You've been wronged.
Dongfang,
I feel bad for you.
I wronged you.
Dongfang...
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Alright, alright,
this is enough.
I'm the one who was wronged.
Why are you crying?
I couldn't tell right from wrong.
I was so heartless!
Aihua, that's enough.
Stop crying.
Don't let the kids see you like this.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Alright, cheers.
Cheers.
Dongfang,
I'm sorry.
My apologies.
I'm so sorry.
Okay.
Alright.
It's okay
since you're here.
Qinglian,
is Aihua okay?
He's always like that when he's drunk.
Just ignore him.
Lingzhi.
Your son, Zihao,
has made his mark.
I heard he won
a world championship playing video games.
The world
is changing so fast.
Are we all getting old?
Alright,
you can just benefit
from your son's success from now on.
Okay.
Let's go.
What success can I benefit from?
He doesn't even
have a girlfriend yet,
unlike your two kids,
who are both big bosses now.
I heard their son, Qi Zhi,
hooked up with Cao Si
right after he got out of prison,
and they were having an affair.
Did you see them flirting
at the table just now?
No wonder Director Zhou's son
divorced her.
What man could tolerate
such a thing?
Exactly.
Aren't you afraid of karma for gossiping
behind people's backs?
Qinglian.
We're all neighbors!
Everyone knows
each other's skeletons in the closet!
Don't make me
spill all your dirty secrets
for everyone to laugh at!
Qinglian, calm down.
What were you two talking about?
Stop gossiping.
What does it have to do with you?
Go away.
Do you
have nothing better to do?
Qinglian,
don't be mad.
Don't stoop to their level.
Qinglian,
I heard that
Cao Si married
into the Zhou family back then
just to get that letter
of forgiveness for Qi Zhi.
Well, Qi Zhi's life was ruined.
But... But didn't Cao Si have her life
ruined as well?
You care so much about these two kids.
Why don't you
allow them to be together?
Right?
You made them?
Not bad.
They're so pretty.
Who did you make them for?
Who do you think I made them for?
Who was crying and begging
to marry someone?
Mom,
you agree to let me and Cao Si
be together?
Is this enough?
Thanks, Mom.
Save it.
Thanks, Mom!
You're the best mother in the world!
Put me down.
You silly boy.
Doudou,
can you tell Grandpa
who your uncle
likes?
Yes, of course.
But Grandpa,
can you help me
with the math problems
my uncle assigned me?
Sure, no problem.
And 5 pages of tracing.
That's fine, too.
Then tell Grandpa
who it is.
The girl my uncle likes is...
Doudou,
what are you doing?
Have you finished
the homework I gave you?
Not yet.
"Not yet"? Then hurry up and do it.
Don't scare the kid.
Go on.
Dad,
you can't keep spoiling him like this.
I'm not spoiling him.
He's just a kid.
Can he finish
all that homework?
Dad,
when I was Doudou's age,
you gave me
way more homework.
You and he
are different.
I dote on my grandchild. So what?
Dad is getting more and more like Grandpa.
Thanks to you,
it feels like our two families
are back to the way we used to be.
How nice.
What brand is your dress?
It's so stylish
with unique buttons.
Prime Era.
Haven't you heard of it?
This brand is really popular now.
I heard there's a meteor shower tonight.
Let's go watch it together?
No. Are you serious?
We've still got a lot to do at the office.
I've already booked tickets
for the observation deck.
They're quite expensive.
I have an appointment
with Mr. Zhang tonight
to discuss business.
What tickets? Are they refundable?
Go return them.
Well...
Which Mr. Zhang?
In the midsummer
of 2010,
the Lyrid meteor shower
arrived as expected,
ready to paint the night sky
with a fabulous spectacle.
At 23:00 on the 22nd,
the Lyrid meteor shower
will reach its peak viewing time.
By then,
countless meteors,
like blooming fireworks,
will light up the night sky
in a dazzling way
and present
a breathtaking visual feast.
Waiting this long to see stars
isn't romantic at all.
I can't see anything here.
How come
the forecast was way off?
If they don't show up,
we'd have waited for nothing.
The forecast was way off.
Let's just go back.
No way.
We can't feed the mosquitoes for nothing.
And your rebellious act
can't go to waste either.
There, look! Look!
A real meteor shower!
Make a wish quickly!
♪ The wind blew through our hair ♪
♪ The story slowly gets complicated too ♪
♪ We never became anyone's myth ♪
♪ We only learned to grow up in the rain ♪
♪ Should we blame fate? ♪
♪ Adulthood is bandaging your own falls ♪
If we hadn't
swapped lives back then,
I might not have become who I am today.
♪ Rented rooms, the last bus home ♪
♪ What does the future hold? ♪
Even though we
took each other's "life scripts,"
♪ It's been so long since I last
dared to say I was afraid ♪
looking back,
everything we've been through
is a gift
from fate.
♪ Though we have nothing,
we still bustle about ♪
Fortunately, having you along the way
allowed me to experience
another kind of life
and made me the best version of myself.
♪ Because the answer is clear
as long as you are around ♪
So,
♪ The old dreams are now covered in dust ♪
we braved the storms
♪ But it's okay ♪
and reached our prime.
There it is! The meteor shower!
♪ The morning glow will finally appear ♪
Make a wish.
♪ Who hasn't panicked
in this fast-paced world? ♪
♪ All I see is your gaze ♪
♪ If there's nothing left tomorrow ♪
♪ I'll still walk you home ♪
You put it up crooked.
Move it left
and then down.
To the left.
Which is it, left or down?
Forget it. Let me help you with it.
Look at you.
How can you not know
how to do anything at your age?
Come on.
Cao Xin and Cao Si used to do this.
Here, help me hold it.
Done.
Nice. Looks good.
Dad!
Qi Shi
opened another shop downtown,
a storefront
of over 140 square meters.
She's got over 1 million followers
on the social media platform
right now.
Over 1 million?
That's so many people.
Qingwu only has a population
of about 10,000.
Think about it.
Our Sweetie
is such a big shot.
Show Mom
the brochure.
Yeah.
Here.
This is their brochure.
Let me see.
Wipe your hands. Hey...
-They're covered with flour.
-Okay.
Beautiful.
Well,
why do their models, um,
look different
from the ones on TV?
Look, there are chubby ones.
And also old ladies.
They've got all kinds of models.
They're just like us
ordinary people, aren't they?
Doesn't this old lady
look like you?
Dad, what are you talking about?
Mom was much prettier
than her when she was young.
I was not this pretty, not this pretty.
Doesn't this one
look like Cao Si?
Like a chubbier version of her?
Try to eat more
until you look like this.
Okay, okay.
This girl looks exactly
like our Sweetie,
so elegant
and pretty.
People's aesthetics are changing now.
You don't have to
look like a model to be
considered pretty.
You're beautiful just being yourself.
Being yourself.
Our Sweetie's shop
has only been open for a few years,
and it's already an internet sensation.
When I walk outside now,
I'm
the father of a celebrity.
Enough, stop bragging.
You feel like a big shot.
I feel like a big shot, you know?
Aihua, Aihua, listen,
don't flatter yourself.
I'm her biological father.
Has she acknowledged that?
Qi Shi's surname is Qi.
She's my daughter.
Why wouldn't she acknowledge it?
She hasn't changed her name,
but that doesn't mean
she hasn't acknowledged it in hear heart.
Can you read her mind?
How do you know what she's thinking?
I just can read her mind.
Cao Xin, Qi Shi,
you're back for New Year's Eve?
They're back.
-Let's take a look.
-They're back.
The kids are back.
Let's go have a look.
There they come.
-Welcome back.
We're back.
-Dad, Mom.
Come inside. We're having dumplings.
Come inside.
Come on in.
♪ Countless times I broke the rules ♪
Come inside quickly.
Sweetie, try this dish.
I made it.
♪ Countless times I longed to break free ♪
Dumplings...
-Dumplings are ready.
-Come on.
♪ I loudly laughed, mocked,
expressed anger, and yelled ♪
♪ Then I realized I missed you dearly ♪
Be careful.
Okay.
-Happy New Year.
♪ Countless times I got emotional ♪
♪ Countless times I learned to express ♪
Happy New Year.
Doudou.
Happy New Year, Doudou.
♪ Love is about doubting numerous times ♪
Let me give you a red envelope.
That's right.
♪ Then reassuring,
yet still not letting go ♪
Give red envelopes, red envelopes.
Okay.
Come on.
♪ Countless times I searched for answers ♪
♪ Could this life be any better? ♪
♪ I was born for my prime ♪
♪ When I open the door ♪
♪ It's our family that never falls apart ♪
♪ They're waiting for me
to come back home ♪